[{"id": 2606, "question": "As the Internet's influence grows, the potential for danger also escalates . One of these dangers is from cyber-bullying. Cyber-bullying is repeatedly hurting someone else through the use of technology. It consists of sending or posting cruel messages, photos, or videos on the Internet or other electronic media with the intent of damaging the reputation of the target. Imagine being a 13-year-old girl discovering a cell phone picture of her changing clothes for gym class has been sent to all her classmates. Or imagine being an 11-year-old boy who is scared to go to school because an unknown bully sent him an instant message saying that he is so fat that he should kill himself. Cases such as these are happening every day, leading kids to be depressed and unable to concentrate. Worse yet, par...\n\nQ: What will probably be discussed in the following passage?", "options": ["How to prevent cyber-bullying.", "What parents and educators think of cyber-bullying.", "How to make parents aware of cyber-bullying.", "How to make good use of technology."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3344, "question": "People with disabilities make up a large part of the population. It is estimated that over 35 million Americans have physical, mental, or other disabilities. About half of these disabilities are \"developmental\", i.e., they occur before the individual's twenty-second birthday, often from genetic conditions, and are severe enough to affect three or more areas of development, such as mobility, communication, employment, etc. Most other disabilities are considered \"adventitious\", i.e., accidental or caused by outside forces. Prior to the 20th century, only a small percentage of people with disabilities survived for long. Medical treatment for these disabilities was unavailable. Advancements in medicine and social services have created a climate in which people with disabilities can expect to h...\n\nQ: In the author's opinion, to enable the disabled people to take their rightful place in society,   _  .", "options": ["more laws should be passed", "public attitudes should be changed", "government should provide more aids", "more public facilities should be set up"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1329, "question": "Jogging has become the most popular individual sport in America. Many theories,even some mystical ones,have been advanced to explain the popularity of jogging. The plain truth is that jogging is a cheap,quick and efficient way to maintain (or achieve) physical fitness. The most useful sort of exercise is exercise that develops the heart,lungs, and circulatory systems. If these systems are fit,the body is ready for almost any sport and for almost any sudden demand made by work or emergencies. One can train more specifically,as by developing strength for weight lifting or the ability to run straight ahead for short distances with great power as in football,but running trains your heart and lungs to deliver oxygen more efficiently to all parts of your body. It is worth doing that: this sort o...\n\nQ: The main purpose of this passage is to   _  ..", "options": ["discuss jogging as a physical fitness program", "describe the type of clothing needed for jogging", "provide scientific evidence of the benefits of jogging", "launch a nationwide physical fitness campaign"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2616, "question": "What is it: Work & Travel USA Who are qualified: Fulltime college students, above 18 years old About the program: Application for the 2009 Work & Travel USA program has just started. It's an 8~16 weeks' summer program for college students to work and travel in the U.S.. Employers include Boeing, Hilton Hotel and 7Eleven. For next summer, about 3,500 positions are open to Chinese students. Applicants must pass a language test and sometimes an interview, and pay a registration fee to join the program. (source : www. Cultureexchange. org) _ What is it: Shanghai Volkswagen jobs Who are qualified: College students graduating in 2009 About it: Shanghai VW offers over 300 positions from engineering to marketing to college students graduating in 2009. Applicants should have an excellent academic r...\n\nQ: The opportunity of   _   is offered only to college students graduating in 2009.", "options": ["working in America", "traveling in America", "positions in VW", "OPI internship"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2449, "question": "Today, Mount Qomolangma's peak is not a lonely place any more. More than 3,500 people have successfully climbed the 8,844m mountain, and more than a tenth of that number reached the peak just over the past year. As more and more people try to test themselves against Qomolangma, many a time the mount can be very crowded. Climbers have complained about waiting for hours in the bottlenecks on the way to the peak. If bad weather strikes, climbers can and do die. But the dangerous crowds aren't the only problem on Qomolangma. All those climbers need to bring a lot of _ --much of them ends up being left on the mountain, sometimes even the peak itself. Mount Qomolangma is becoming the world's tallest rubbish dump. Here's mountaineer Mark Jenkins writing in National Geographic about the state of Q...\n\nQ: What do we learn about the bottlenecks on the way to Mount Qomolangma's peak?", "options": ["They are relatively safe.", "They are often crowded.", "They are very easy to pass.", "They are sites of base camps."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 255, "question": "It should be very clear that we live in a most spectacular time. It's a time when information is of primary importance. It's a time when new information technologies are fundamentally transforming the world in every aspect. Among the changes, which have come upon modern society, the ones in education are probably the most obvious and influential. New information technologies are accelerating changes in education, at the same time presenting revolutionary tools with the potential to make education more efficient and more effective than ever. The application of new information technologies has remarkably promoted the process of education. Online learning is probably the best case in point. As is often the case with \"technology\", online learning may appear to be horrible; it can sound like al...\n\nQ: Which of the following descriptions about online learning is NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["It is more efficient and effective.", "It is convenient to both teachers and students.", "It stresses interactions between teachers and students.", "It is a cheaper way of learning."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3239, "question": "NEW YORK--Microsoft on Monday made another effort to challenge Apple's iPhone and Google's Android in the exploding smartphone market--launching a wireless operating system,Windows Phone 7. Consumers will consider it\"always delightful and thoroughly mine,\"Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer said at a launch event. Ballmer said last year that Microsoft had\" _ \"with its Windows Mobile operating system.For example,it failed to keep up with touch-screen innovations that make iPhones and Android phones easy to use. Microsoft fell from third to fourth place in market share this year,behind BlackBerry,iPhone and Android. Only 10.8% of smartphone owners used Microsoft's system in August,down from 18% last December. But Windows Phone 7 is\"a total departure from anything they've done\".Microsoft says it soug...\n\nQ: Which of the following phones will NOT use Windows Phone 7 operating system?", "options": ["Quantum.", "Surround.", "Android.", "Focus."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2875, "question": "For thousands of years, mankind has produced plants and animals to create more desired and useful plants and animals. For example, modern com has been produced to such a large size that it is no longer able to reproduce without man's assistance. Modern dairy cows produce too much milk and if they are not often emptied of milk, they could leak, burst, become infected, and possibly die. Besides, most dogs raised by people can not survive in the wild even with special training. Since natural evolution is extremely slow and mankind's selective production programs only take a few generations to produce a completely new species, natural evolution has already _ mankind's production programs. In addition, mankind has successfully killed off several species all together. For example, there are no m...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Near-sighted parents will be able to produce babies with good eyesight in the future.", "Doctors and scientists will be responsible for mass production of babies in the future.", "It is natural evolution that is to blame for the destruction of European wolves and mammoths.", "Children can now have their memory and intelligence improved with the help of gene treatment."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1509, "question": "Since my son is getting ready for first grade, I asked a friend where she shops for school supplies. For price and convenience, she had a quick answer: schoolpak.com. Parents can buy items or packaged equipment for all grades. The Generic Elementary School-pak for first through fifth graders, for example, is $23.28. (Teachers can also e-mail their grade's or school's whole list for a price on customized kits . Shipping is free for 75 or more kits) _ Teachers thinks highly of educationalwarehouse.com for its learning tools and games--everything from puzzles and puppets to software and chalks.Classroomdirect.com has great prices on over 10.000 products and a special corner offering even deeper discounts. Pick your lunch box The second-most-difficult back-to-school decision, right after what ...\n\nQ: What can be filled in the blank in the first item?", "options": ["Teachers are much wiser", "Puzzles and puppets", "Shops where teachers shop", "Develop your brains"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 790, "question": "It was almost six years ago that my family and I waited for her at the airport. Unsure of what to expect and a little bitter about such an experience that my mother was forcing upon me, I had mixed feeling about the girl from Madrid. Today,after making many memories and discoveries, I couldn't be more thankful for what that experience taught me. My family had the privilege to host Teresa for several summers. I became fond of her cheerful chatter, constant laughter ,and addiction to online shopping. She seldom took my unkind jokes seriously and always gave it right back to me, making our relationship closer. She could go on talking for hours about the beach outside her house, her family and friends, and her life at her school. While several aspects were very similar to my life here, I was a...\n\nQ: What is the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Learning Foreign Languages", "Getting Better Culture", "Close Tie with Teresa", "Hosting Teresa"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 451, "question": "No one is sure how the ancient Egyptians built the pyramids near Cairo. But a new study suggests they used a little rock'n'roll. Long-ago builders could have attached wooden poles to the stones and rolled them across the sand, the scientists say. \"Technically, I think what they're proposing is possible,\" physicist Daniel Bonn said. People have long puzzled over how the Egyptians moved such huge rocks. And there's no obvious answer. On average, each of the two million big stones weighed about as much as a large pickup truck. The Egyptians somehow moved the stone blocks to the pyramid site from about one kilometer away. The most popular view is that Egyptian workers slid the blocks along smooth paths. Many scientists suspect wokers first would have put the blocks on sleds . Then they would h...\n\nQ: It's widely believed that the stone blocks were moved to the pyramid site by   _  .", "options": ["rolling them on roads", "pushing them over the sand", "dragging them on some poles", "sliding them on smooth paths"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 940, "question": "Shoppers who have cut back on purchases in the worrying U.S. economy are likely to continue their conservative shopping habits even if the economy improves, according to a new study. That signals continued bad news for retailers , who have been struggling to respond to a great cutback in spending as consumers have opened their wallets only for basic items, while cutting back on unimportant purchases. The report, which estimates retail sales growth to be flat this year, found that three-quarters of respondents to a monthly survey of 4,000 consumers said they had shifted their shopping behaviors because of the economy. Most said they were making do with less or going without some favorite items. \"The habits learned during this economic crisis have the potential to permanently change the mind...\n\nQ: According to the report,   _  .", "options": ["bigger shops will be more successful", "supermarkets do better than super centers", "clothing will recover smoothly in 2010", "most respondents suffer from the crisis"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 907, "question": "Under new rules posted by the Civil Aviation administration of China on Friday, pilots will have to pass a \"level four\" test of Mandarin Chinese, China's official language. Those who speak with an accent that \"often impedes\" comprehension will not pass. These rules take effect in January 2016. China's 56 ethnic groups speak more than 80 languages and dialects. Even native Mandarin speakers can have trouble communicating with each other depending on the strength of their accents, which can be mutually unintelligible . One flight trainer illustrated the scope for linguistic confusion, especially when common English aviation terms are used. Asked if there is a problem on board, a Chinese pilot might answer in the negative with the words mei you, or \"there isn't. But someone speaking with a he...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Chinese Pilots Told to Get Rid of Regional Accents.", "Chinese Pilots.", "Rich Chinese Languages.", "Hard to Be a Chinese Pilot."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 941, "question": "It was near dusk, and Kim Cooper and her husband, Steve, were trucking through northern Kentucky transportation auto parts from Louisville to Detroit for a goods company. \"Steve, wake up!\" she shouted. \"There's a truck on fire!\" Inside the burning truck, Ronnie Sanders, 38, was fighting for his life. He'd been running a heavy load of tractors and forklifts from Georgia to Indianapolis when a van in front of him stopped suddenly in traffic on the icy road. As Ronnie bore down, he could see children in the backseat. The truck's bulk would probably protect him from the worst of the impact, but the force of 23 tons would likely crush everyone inside the van. \"I figured instead of killing other people, I'd just put the truck in the ditch.\" At the bottom, rocks cut a fuel tank, which caught fire...\n\nQ: According to the passage, Ronnie put the truck in the ditch because of   _  .", "options": ["his concern for his own safety", "his poor driving skill", "the icy road", "his concern for others' lives"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2717, "question": "Holiday houses in Mallorca sailing and fishing port - quiet even in summer season. Beautifully situated houses with sights of sea and mountains, yet near to shops and restaurants. Cars and bicycles for hire. Sailing and sports clubs nearby. ITALY IN COMFORT Luxury coach( - carriage) trips of Italy, out of normal holiday season. 21days to visit five Italian cities starting from London 1 st May, 1 st September . The trips are guided by profess or Martin Davis. Head of Italian Studies, London University . See the arts and culture of historic Italy. KIBBUTZ HOLIDAYS IN ISRAEL Working holidays on a kibbutz( co -operative farm) in Israel. All nationalities welcome for one to three months, if prepared to work morning with kibbutz members. Accommodation , food and trips to historic sights all prov...\n\nQ: Michael would most probably go to   _   for his holiday.", "options": ["Italy", "Israel", "Mallorca", "a Caribbean island"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 664, "question": "The woman had died when the rescuers found her after the terrible earthquake. She was covered by a destroyed house. Through gaps of those ruins,the rescuers could see her last posture . It was something like an ancient person who was kowtowing ,but it just looked strange because she was out of shape by pressure. The rescuers confirmed her death by touching her through the gaps of the ruins. They shouted at the ruins again and again,knocked the bricks using various tools,but no reply inside. Then the rescuing team went to the next building. Suddenly the leader ran back,calling \"Come here.\" He came to the body,put his hands under the woman,feeling and touching,then shouted loudly and gladly,\"There is someone,a baby,still living.\" Through some efforts,rescuers cleaned up the ruins which block...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about    .", "options": ["a story of saving a mother and her baby", "the disaster of a terrible earthquake", "the rescuers' hard work after an earthquake", "the great love of a mother in the earthquake"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 983, "question": "NEW DELHI, India (AP)--India is fast becoming a top destination for tourists thanks to a forceful campaign to push the country's Himalayan spas and beaches, officials say. Tourism officials have been crisscrossing the globe as part of the government's \"Incredible India\" campaign launched in 2003. And the results are beginning to show. Tourists traveling to prefix = st1 /Indiahave jumped by nearly 26 percent from last year and the number is expected to cross 3 million this year, said Amitabh Kant, chairman of the India Tourism Development Corp. \"Foreign exchange earnings, too, have shown a nearly 40 percent rise this year,\" Kant told The Associated Press. India's earnings from tourism were $4.3 billion between January and November 2004, compared to $3.1 billion for the same period of 2003. ...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["tourism in India", "India's technique", "the future of India", "India's position in people's mind"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2708, "question": "The word proactivity is fairly common in management literature, but you won't find it in the dictionary. It means that as a human being you take responsibility for your own life. Look at the word responsibility: ability to choose your response, response-ability. Effective people are proactive because they take responsibility. Their behavior is a product of their own decisions, based on values, rather than being a product of their own conditions, based on feelings.For instance, you are planning a picnic with your family.You're excited.You have all the preparations.You've decided where to go, and then it becomes stormy, killing your plan.Proactive people . They realize what their purpose really was, and they creatively have a picnic elsewhere even if it's in their own basement with some spec...\n\nQ: According to the passage, a proactive person's behavior can result from    _   .", "options": ["the environment", "an inner belief", "the genetic makeup", "a temporary feeling"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2494, "question": "Sir, The majority(=Most) of your readers must have been surprised and shocked to read a letter from Mr.R.Hogg,published in last Wednesday's Herald.Mr.Hogg seems to think that his own convenience and that of motorists in general are the only things that matter in our city. I would have supported Mr.Hogg if he had just made suggestions to improve the situation.No doubt his problems would be partly solved if the local government built a multi-storey car park in the city center,instead of encouraging motorists to use public transport.All the same,judging from the tone of Mr.Hogg's letter,I suspect that motorists who are so careless of pedestrians' safety that they would rather park their ears on the pavement than hold up the traffic would probably be too lazy to use a multi-storey car park if ...\n\nQ: The topic for the two letters is  _  .", "options": ["parking problems in the city center", "building a multi-storey car park in the city center", "public transport", "the increase in accidents caused by parked cars on the pavement"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 561, "question": "The USA Well, imagine how my sister felt when she went off for the first time to New York for a business trip. After a few days she was still amazed at how friendly everyone was to her until she took a taxi back to her hotel one night. First she gave just the name of the hotel, but when asked she said the address too. Then she was asked how to get there, but of course she didn't know. Imagine how frightened she was when the driver started shouting at her for not knowing the way. The UK A friend was in London for a conference. He took a taxi and there were no problems: the driver knew the way and was very cheerful. The problem started when he realized he had stupidly left his laptop on the back seat! He called the company up and, in a panic, went straightaway to their Lost and Found office....\n\nQ: Why couldn't the author's brother find a taxi in Tunis?", "options": ["Because it was too late.", "Because the weather was bad.", "Because he didn't know how to call a taxi.", "Because the taxi drivers disappeared on purpose."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2120, "question": "Dubai, the Gulf desert city state, which is well-known for its huge projects before it was hit by the global financial crisis , on Saturday announced a new development to open the world's biggest mall and a park larger than London's Hyde Park. The ruler of the Gulf desert city state, Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid al-Maktoum, announced the plan for a \"new city within Dubai\", according to an official statement, naming it after himself. No cost was stated for \"Mohammed bin Rashid City,\" to be carried out by his private companies, which developed many of Dubai's well-known projects, including Burj Khalifa, the world's tallest tower. The \"Mall of the World\" will attract 80 million visitors a year to become the \"largest in the world,\" said the statement, while its park will be \"30 percent bigger th...\n\nQ: Which would be the best title of the news?", "options": ["Tourism and Hotel Profits Growing in Dubai", "Biggest Mall to be Developed In Dubai", "Global Financial Crisis Hit Dubai", "Plan to Rebuild Dubai Announced"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1632, "question": "Most people consider skydiving a product of the 20th century, but its history actually goes further back than that. The Chinese attempted to parachute in the 10th century, a thousand years before we did. The Chinese did what we would today call base diving; that is, they jumped off a place that would allow them to float from a height to the ground. The first person to attempt to parachute was a Frenchman named Jacques Garnerin. He jumped from his hot-air balloon at the end of the 18th century and did tricks on the way down and _ the crowds by landing safely on the ground. At the end of the 19th century, Kathie Paulus, a brave German woman, became famous for her skydiving skills. Once the airplane was invented, skydiving took on a whole new form. The airplane made it possible to dive from g...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Skydiving is not a military action any more.", "Kathie Paulus is famous for her skydiving skills.", "The first person who parachuted was from Germany.", "The history of skydiving is longer than that of parachuting."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2298, "question": "Law School Essays that Made a Difference Price: US $ 13.95 Paperback 256 pages The Princeton Review ISBN: 0375763457 Face it, and a lot of students have great LSAT scores. The best way for you to stand out in a crowd of applicants to top law schools is to write an exceptional(,) personal statement. This book puts you in the admissions office's seat. It gives you the intimate detailstest scores, GPAs (grade point average), demographic information, and personal statementsof 34 law school hopefuls, then shows you why they got into the colleges they applied to, and why some didn't. It's invaluable information that will help students evaluate their own chances of admission to the most selective law schools in the United States. Business School Essays that Made a Difference Price: US $ 13.95 Pap...\n\nQ: With the three books, the Princeton Review aims at   _  .", "options": ["offering students guides in making a difference in their jobs after university graduation", "offering guides on the writing of application essays for American universities", "showing students how to pass LSA T in the US", "showing college graduates what helped actual students achieve their dreams"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1948, "question": "Artie Shaw was born in New York City in 1910. His name was Arthur Arshawsky. His parents were poor immigrants who had come to the United States from Eastern Europe. His family later moved to New Haven, Connecticut. At the age of fourteen, he began to play the saxophone and then the clarinet. From a very young age, Artie Shaw wanted to play his clarinet better than anyone. He wanted his sound and music to be perfect. He worked at this task much of his life. He began working as a professional musician when he was fifteen. He left home and began playing in bands across the United States. In 1928, young Artie Shaw traveled to Chicago, Illinois to hear the great trumpet player, Louis Armstrong. He immediately understood that Armstrong's great jazz sound was the beginning of something new and ex...\n\nQ: Which one can be the title of the passage?", "options": ["Artie Shaw's Life Stories", "Artie Shaw -- A Crazy Musician", "Artie Shaw -- A Great Writer", "Artie Shaw's Music Life"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3338, "question": "Mars is the planet most like Earth.Flying to Mars is a difficult task for humans. There is an experiment with the name \"Mars 500\" in Russia.Six volunteers take part in the experiment.They come from China, Russia, France and Italy.They won't go to outer space.They will stay in small modules on the ground for 520 days.It's just like a real journey In the modules, they will experience a lot: flying to Mars, flying back and working on Mars.During the long \"journey\", the volunteers can only eat space food.They can shower every 10 days.They can call their friends or families.Anyone of them can _ if he doesn't feel well.This experiment helps scientists know how well humans will be on a long journey to Mars. Wangyue, 26, from China, is the youngest of the volunteers.He is a teacher at the China As...\n\nQ: Where can you read the article?", "options": ["story book", "geography magazines", "science magazines", "magazines about ET"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 248, "question": "Worn by the rich and famous around the world and now a $799.04 million-a-year enterprise , Ugg boots have come a long way since their 1973 creation--designed to keep surfers' feet warm in cold Australian conditions. Twenty-eight years after selling the rights to his woollen-lined creation, Aussie Ugg boot inventor Shane Stedman says he has no regrets though missing out on a great footwear fortune . A lifelong surfer, Mr. Stedman, now 69, who lives at beachside Mona Vale in Sydney, said his invention grew from need. \"The sea is bloody cold in the Aussie winter...I used to wear football jerseys to keep them (feet) warm\", Mr. Stedman said. But his sheepskin invention soon solved the problem and Mr. Stedman went on to spend a decade selling the sturdy boots, until 1983 when he sold the rights ...\n\nQ: From the text we know that Ugg boots are mostly made of the skin of   _  .", "options": ["wolves", "sheep", "pigs", "cows"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1822, "question": "Earth Day events are arranged all over the world, but for New Yorkers in the Catskill region, there are plenty of options.s6t---- Earth Day Celebrations6t---- Place: Frost Valley; Time: Friday, April 8 - Saturday, April 9 (Check-in at 5:00 pm on Friday). Activities include recycled arts and crafts projects, classes on composting and recycling, nature hikes, and a greenhouse planting project. All ages are welcomed. $15.00 per person (includes lunch). Kids 5 and under free. Call (845) 985-2291 for more details and to register.s6t---- Earth Festivals6t---- Place: Milford Central School; Time: Saturday, April 9 (11:00 am - 3:00 pm). Enjoy exhibits, activities and entertainment. Bring along your recyclables to be collected. You'll go green! Fashion Show will be held at the end of the day. Admis...\n\nQ: If you want to get tickets to the fashion show, you should call   _  .s6t----", "options": ["(845) 985-2291", "(518) 829-7516", "(607) 286-7721s6t----", "(607) 547-4488"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 122, "question": "If you go into the woods with your friends, stay with them. If you don't, you may get lost. If you do get lost, this is what you should do. Sit down and stay where you are. Don't try to find your friends -- let them find you. You can help them to find you by staying in one place. There is another way to help your friends or other people nearby to find you. Give them a signal by shouting or whistling three times. Stop. Then shout or whistle three times again. Any signal given three times is a call for help. You will be helped by others. Keep up the shouting or whistling, always three times together. When people hear you, they will know that you are not just making noise for fun. They will let you know they have heard your signal. They will give two shouts, two whistles or two gunshots. When...\n\nQ: If nobody answers you after your signal, what should you do then?", "options": ["Give two gunshots.", "Shout louder.", "Stop shouting.", "Make a house."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1379, "question": "One day a father and his rich family took his son on a trip to the country with the firm purpose to show him how poor people can be. They spent a day and a night on the farm of a very poor family. When they got back from their trip, the father asked his son, \"How was the trip?\" \"Very good, Dad!\" \"Did you see how poor people can be?\" the father asked. \"Yeah!\" \"And what did you learn?\" The son answered, \"I saw that we have a dog at home, and they have four. We have a pool that reaches to the middle of the garden; they have a creek that has no end. We have imported lamps in the garden; they have the stars. Our patio reaches to the front yard; they have a whole horizon.\" When the little boy finished, his father was speechless. The son added, \"Thanks, Dad, for showing me how poor we are!\" Isn't...\n\nQ: The son's father and family went to the country to_.", "options": ["see beautiful scenery", "see poor people there", "see some children", "see a long river there"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3212, "question": "Every day is a gift, and if you look forward to spending each day with happiness, wake up every morning with a positive attitude and enjoy a beautiful day! Set up a daily plan for yourself and ensure that you reserve enough time for your homework. Also, don't forget to spare some time for play! Stop being lazy and start participating in your life instead of just watching it pass by. Try to do something fun and constructive every day. _ , write something interesting in your diary, try a new hobby, spend time with your friends, or just watch your favorite show on television, and you will see how every moment of your day unfolds. You'll achieve better results, and ultimately greater success. However, every day will not be the way you want it to be. Some days will be good, while some will be b...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["Planning your schedule for the next day the night before.", "Getting into the habit of self-praising with goals achieved.", "Rising early to get ready for your day with positive energy.", "Trying something new to learn from it to stretch your limits."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2308, "question": "Engineers should embrace the arts, Sir John O'Reilly, a fellow of the Institution of Engineering and Technology, argued in a lecture. About 59% of engineering companies in the IET's 2014 survey feared skill shortages could threaten business. \"There is nothing as creative as engineering,\" Sir John told the reporter. He says science, technology, engineering and mathematics - often known as \"Stem\" subjects, are vital for a modern knowledge economy. But there is a massive shortfall in the number of recruits - with a recent study by the Royal Academy of Engineering saying the UK needs to increase by as much as 50% the number of Stem graduates it produces. Delivering this year's Mountbatten Lecture at the Royal Institution, Sir John argued that engineers should recognise the role of the arts in ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["More university students should study arts instead of engineering.", "Engineering and technology is increasingly different and unrelated fields.", "The IET's skills survey raised concerns about the number of recruits to engineering.", "Students from some university engineering departments have already transferred to art schools"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2436, "question": "May 28 (Reuters Life!) - A Japanese university is giving away Apple Inc's (AAPL.O) trendy iPhone to students for free, but with a catch: the device will be used to check their attendance. The project, which is being tested ahead of its formal launch in June, involves 550 first and second year students and some staff of a department at Aoyama Gakuin University, which is located just outside Tokyo in Sagamihara city. The school's iPhones are meant to create a mobile information network between students and professors, but they are also a convenient way for the teachers to take attendance in class. As students enter the room, instead of writing their name on a sheet, they simply type in their ID number and a specific class number into an iPhone application. To prevent students from logging in...\n\nQ: what about the future of Apple Inc's iphone", "options": ["It still has many disadvantages", "It goes against many students' interest", "It will receive some other uses.", "It will avoid students' being late for class"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2661, "question": "Along a long path we came to a deep valley, on the far side of which the path led into some very thick bushes. Rather than push through up again and rejoin the path on the far side of the bushes As I climbed down into the valley a bird flew off h rock on which I had put my hand. On looking at the spot from which the bird had risen, I saw two eggs. They were the kind that I did not have in my collection, so I placed them carefully in my bag, wrapped in a little dry grass. As we went further down the valley the sides became steeper and not far from where I had entered. It came to drop of about twelve to fourteen feet. The water that rushed down all these small valleys in the rainy season had worn the rock as glass. As it was too deep to climb down, I handed my gun to one of the men and slid ...\n\nQ: Which of the following orders is RIGHT about what happened in their travel?", "options": ["hear the sound of tiger-find eggs-push through the bushes-climb down into the valley", "climb down into the valley-push through the bushes-hear the sound of tiger-find eggs", "push through the bushes-climb down into the valley-find eggs-hear the sound of tiger", "find eggs-climb down into the valley-hear the sound of tiger-push through the bushes"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2558, "question": "You may have heard of the book Moby Dick(<<>> ), written by the American author Herman Melville. You may also know that Moby Dick is considered one of the greatest novels ever written. However, it might surprise you to find out Herman Melville was not always a highly regarded author. Melville's first two novels, Typee and Omoo, were widely read and financially successfully. They were both exciting tales of adventures at sea and experiences with people in foreign lands. Melville became quite famous. However, upon the publication of his third book, Mardi, Melville's popularity began to weaken. He was no longer interested in telling tales of pure adventure, and his writing took on a style that alienated the general reading public of his time. Melville published Moby Dick in October of 1851. i...\n\nQ: We can learn from the text that Moby Dick  _  .", "options": ["sold a little better than Pierre.", "was Melville's favorite novel.", "was copied from other books.", "made Melville popular again."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1114, "question": "If you wish to dance with a certain lady, go to her, bow, and say, \"May I have the pleasure of a dance?\" If it is a formal dance with programs, she will tell you which dance she will have with you; if there are no programs, she will either rise and dance with you, or she may say, \"I have this dance taken.\" Or she may say, \"I am sorry, I am not dancing this dance.\" This may be a polite way of saying that she does not want to dance with you, or it may be that she is tired and wants to rest; you will have to judge which is her attitude. Do not expect a lady whom you have invited to dance in advance for a dance to make any attempt to find you. It is her part to remain seated until you find her. Bow and say, \"I believe this is my dance.\" At the end of a dance, thank your partner, but do not lea...\n\nQ: If you have already made an appointment with a lady at the ball,  _  .", "options": ["it is her duty to find you", "it is still your duty to find her", "it is both of your duty to find each other", "you wait and wait until it is your turn to dance with her"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1266, "question": "I live in north Celebes which is near Philippines. Since early December 2010 most tropical regions have been frequently hit by rain. Just like my hometown, tropical regions only have two seasons, including the dry season that usually starts from April to September and the wet or rainy season which usually happens from October to March. But, it could be _ Sometimes the rainy season can come a month earlier or later. It can be prolonged even more than 4 months and so can the dry season. Even during the dry season, rain can occur several times in certain areas. The prolonged dry season in tropical areas usually causes a lot of losses. It will be very harmful to local farmers, because most of the tropical areas sre regions of the developing countries. Sometimes agricultural and plantation crop...\n\nQ: The main purpose of this passage is to introduce   _  .", "options": ["some interesting facts of tropical regions", "some knowledge about tropical regions to travelers", "some knowledge about how to live well in different regions.", "some differences between dry and wet seasons in tropical regions."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1747, "question": "Where is that noise coming from? Not sure? Try living with your eyes closed for a few years. Blind people are better at locating sounds than people who can see, a new study says, without the benefits of vision the ears seem to work much better. Previous studies have shown that blind people are better than others at reaching out and touching the sources of sounds that are close by. Researchers from the University of Montreal wanted to see if blind people were also better at locating sounds that are far away. Twenty-three blind people participated in the study. All had been sightless for at least 20 years. Fourteen of them had lost their vision before age 11. the rest went blind after age 16. The experiment also included 10 people who could see but were wearing blind-folds. In one task, volu...\n\nQ: The recent study shows blind people are better at telling   _  .", "options": ["The sources of loud sounds.", "the locations of distant sounds", "the direction of sharp sounds", "the distance of a sound in front of them"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2159, "question": "Borrowing to start a business is not easy. Getting a bank loan, particularly for a new small business, is _ Banks favor established-business people with a solid credit rating and a large bank account. They should also have experience in the business they propose to enter, and offer well-prepared business plans that show the ability to repay the loans. If you are not such a person, then you need to double your preparations to convince the banker to lend you that much needed start-up capital . If your business is new and small, bankers will need to know as much as possible about you and your business. However, many small business owners often make the mistake of not being well prepared when going to the bank to apply for the loan. Surprisingly, many loan applicants don't even have the slight...\n\nQ: Some small businesses fail to get a bank loan because   _  .", "options": ["the form they fill in is incomplete", "their products are not technically advanced", "the amount of money they want to borrow is too big", "they have no clear idea of how much they need to borrow"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 873, "question": "I must have been about fourteen then, and I put away the incident from my mind with the easy carelessness of youth. But the words, Carl Walter spoke that day, came back to me years later, and ever since have been of great value to me. Carl Walter was my piano teacher. During one of my lessons he asked how much practicing I was doing. I said three or four hours a day. \"Do you practice , an hour at a time?\" \"I try to.\" \"Well, don't,\" he exclaimed. \"When you grow up, time won't come in long stretches. Practice in minutes, whenever you can find them five or ten before school, after lunch, between household tasks. Spread the practice through the day, and piano-playing will become a part of your life.\" When I was teaching at Columbia, I wanted to write, but class periods, theme-reading, and comm...\n\nQ: We can infer that the writer    _    .", "options": ["has new books published each year however busy his teaching is", "is always tired of interruptions in life because his teaching schedule is always heavy", "has formed a bad habit of chewing a pencil while writing his novels", "can find sufficient time for mental preparations beforehand, so he's devoted to work instantly"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1739, "question": "Names have gained increasing importance in the competitive world of higher education. As colleges struggle for market share, they are looking for names that project the image they want or reflect the changes they hope to make. Trenton State College, for example, became the College of New Jersey nine years ago when it began raising admission standards and appealing to students from throughout the state. \"All I hear in higher education is, 'Brand, brand, brand,'\" said Tim Westerbeck, who specializes in branding and is managing director of Lippmann Hearne, a marketing firm based in Chicago that works with universities and other nonprofit organizations. \"There has been a sea change over the last 10 years. Marketing used to be almost a dirty word in higher education.\" Not all efforts at name ch...\n\nQ: The phrase \"come up with\" (Line 3, Para. 4) probably means   _  .", "options": ["catch up with", "deal with", "put forward", "come to the realization"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1363, "question": "Tom appeared on the sidewalk with a bucket of whitewash and a long-handled brush. He stopped by the fence in front of the house where he lived with his aunt Polly. He looked at it, and all joy left him. The fence was long and high. He put the brush into the whitewash and moved it along the top of the fence. He repeated the operation. He felt he could not continue and sat down. He knew that his friends would arrive soon with all kinds of interesting plans for the day. They would walk past him and laugh. They would make jokes about his having to work on a beautiful summer Saturday. The thought burned him like fire. He put his hand into his pockets and took out all that he owned. Perhaps he could find some way to pay someone to do the whitewashing for him. But there was nothing of value in hi...\n\nQ: How many characters are mentioned in this story?", "options": ["7", "6", "5", "4"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3051, "question": "One warm September night, Mira had come down to the beach to enjoy the night air. She closed her eyes and listened to the waves. Suddenly, she could hear another sound, so she opened her eyes and looked down at the sand. It was moving! All of a sudden she could see a tiny head coming out. Then a turtle appeared! One by one they struggled out of their underground nests. Mira looked in surprise at the baby turtles. Mira knew the turtles should head towards the waves and swim away, so she was puzzled when they began to pull themselves towards the dunes . Suddenly, she remembered something her grandmother had told her. \"Sea turtles bury their eggs on the beach every year in April and in September. Those baby turtles hatch and head back down to the sea. But some of them never make it. Sometimes...\n\nQ: Where did the story happen?", "options": ["On a beach at night", "In a house near the dunes.", "On a front porch in the evening.", "In the shallow water of the ocean."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1546, "question": "About ten years ago, a young and very successful businessman named Josh was traveling down a Chicago neighborhood street. He was going a bit too fast in his shiny, black, 12 cylinder Jaguar XKE, which was only two months old. He was watching for kids rushing out from between parked cars and slowed down when he thought he saw something. As his car passed, no child came out, but a brick sailed out and - WHUMP! - it hit the Jaguar's shiny black side door! SCREECH ... ! ! ! ! Immediately Josh stopped the car, jumped out, seized the kid and pushed him up against a parked car. He shouted at the kid, \"What was that all about and who are you? Just what the heck are you doing?!\" \"That's my new Jaguar, that brick you threw is gonna cost you a lot of money. Why did you throw it?\" \"Please, mister, ple...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the last sentence means   _  .", "options": ["trying to be more understanding seeing others in trouble", "trying to get ready for the trouble in your future life", "driving fast in a neighborhood street is dangerous", "protecting oneself from being hurt"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1497, "question": "Love Is Just a Thread Sometimes I really doubt whether there is love between my parents.Every day they are very busy trying to earn money to pay the high tuition for us.They don't act in the romantic ways that I read in books or I see on TV.\" I love you\" is too luxurious for them to say .Sending flowers to each other on Valentine's Day is even more _ .My father is easy to lose his temper, especially when he's very tired from the hard work. One day, my mother was sewing a quilt.I silently sat beside her and asked her if there was love between them.\" What?\" she replied, still doing her work.My mother stopped her work and raised her head with surprise.She didn't answer immediately.Then she bowed her head and continued sewing the quilt.I was in a great embarrassment and I didn't know what to d...\n\nQ: What made her father change so greatly?", "options": ["The real love.", "The thread of the quilt.", "The beautiful scenery of the country road.", "All the other members of the family."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3464, "question": "Choosing the Right Resolution Millions of Americans began 2014 with the same resolution they started 2013 with, a goal of losing weight. However, setting weight loss as a goal is a mistake. To reach our goal of losing weight --- the output, we need to control what we eat --- the input ( ). That is, we tend to care about the output but not to control the input. This is a bad way to construce goals. The alternative is to focus your resolution on the input. Instead of resolving to lose weight, try an actionable resolution: \"I'll stop having desert for lunch,\" or \"I'll walk every day for 20 minutes.\" Creating a goal that focuses on a well-specified input will likely be more effective than concentrating on the outcome. Recently a new science behind incentives , including in education, has been ...\n\nQ: In Roland Fryer's research, some students did better than the others because   _   .", "options": ["they obeyed all the general rules", "they paid more attention to exams", "they were motivated by their classmates", "they were rewarded for reading some books"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3136, "question": "For some reason, it takes constant reminders that weprimates need nurturing. In a recent study of 46 babychimpanzee orphans, Kim Bard of the University of Portsmouth in England and her colleagues demonstrated that primate babies that have tight relationships with mother figures do much better oncognitive tests than babies who receive only food, shelter, and friendship with peers. But this is not breaking mews. In fact, it's old news. In the 1950s, Harry Harlow conducted a series of experiments with baby monkeys that showed, without doubt, that lack of love and comfort makes for a crazy monkey. Harlow constructed a cage that included a wire monkey \"mother\" topped with a plastic face. In this wire he fixed Mom with a milk bottle. The cage also held another wire mother covered with terry clot...\n\nQ: Harlow built two \"mothers\" for baby monkeys to   _  .", "options": ["make them live comfortably", "let them have more choices", "give them more love", "make a comparison"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1362, "question": "Never before in Chinese history has a documentary film aroused so much public enthusiasm. Everybody is talking about a new 7-part documentary called A Bite of China which was recently broadcast late at night on CCTV I. The documentary describes various _ across the vast Chinese culinary landscape. According to Taobao, China's biggest online retail website, just five days after the series began to air, nearly 6 million people went to the site in search of various local specialties, particularly those mentioned in the documentary. More than 7.2 million deals were concluded. A ham producer from Yunnan Province saw his sales grow 17-fold in five days. However, one can't help but believe that the documentary's popularity is probably linked to the endless stream of terrible food security issues ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, China's food industry is full of faking and cheating because  _  .", "options": ["there are still so many poor people at the present time", "the punishment for unscrupulous businessmen isn't serious enough", "the Chinese government encourages it to do so", "the food technology is not so advanced as in developed countries"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3373, "question": "Farmer John and Farmer Bob were neighbors. For more than 30 years, they had been getting along very well. Then their good relationship broke. It began with a small thing, then bitter words, and then weeks of silence. One morning Farmer John woke up to find a stream between the two farms. \"It must be Bob,\" John thought. Then one day there was a knock on John's door. He opened it to find a carpenter standing at the doorway. \"I'm looking for a few days' work,\" the carpenter said. \"I do have a job for you,\" John said. \"Look across the stream at that farm. That's my neighbor Bob. He dug a stream between the two farms. I want you to build a fence--an 8-foot fence. I don't want to see his place or his face any more. I don't have such a neighbor!\" The carpenter said, \"I think I know what to do, si...\n\nQ: What does the sentence \"You're quite a fellow to build this bridge!\" mean?", "options": ["John was great to build this bridge.", "John was not good at building bridges.", "John was foolish to build such a bridge.", "John should build the bridge earlier."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 939, "question": "Shoppers who have cut back on purchases in the worrying U.S. economy are likely to continue their conservative shopping habits even if the economy improves, according to a new study. That signals continued bad news for retailers , who have been struggling to respond to a great cutback in spending as consumers have opened their wallets only for basic items, while cutting back on unimportant purchases. The report, which estimates retail sales growth to be flat this year, found that three-quarters of respondents to a monthly survey of 4,000 consumers said they had shifted their shopping behaviors because of the economy. Most said they were making do with less or going without some favorite items. \"The habits learned during this economic crisis have the potential to permanently change the mind...\n\nQ: What will the consumers do with the worrying US economy?", "options": ["Having existing stores target local markets.", "Going without some favorite items.", "Giving up their near-term shopping plan.", "Opening their wallets for daily buying."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 681, "question": "For the first time in Hong Kong's history, an entertainer has been written into middle school textbooks. He is considered one of the best actors in Hong Kong. Yes, he is Chow Yun-fat. The example of his long hard struggle for success has been used in a chapter in a Hong Kong middle school textbook. Using his experience, students can learn to make the most of their time and to grab every opportunity to succeed. On hearing about this, Chow said happily, \"I really hope that my experiences can make young people understand that one should not be afraid of difficulties and setbacks , for they are the only way to success.\" Indeed, Chow has travelled a long and difficult path to reach his success. In 1955, he was born into a poor family in Hong Kong. When he was 17, he had to leave school. He work...\n\nQ: Chow Yun-fat has been written into middle school textbooks mainly because   _  .", "options": ["he plays best in Hong Kong", "he keeps on struggling for success", "his experiences are very special", "he is well thought of"], "answer": 1}]